Do you have too many pairs of shoes or old gadgets lying around the house?
你家里是不是有太多双鞋子或者旧的小器具到处乱放呢？
I'm sure many of us have a lot of things that we don't really use and when things get out of hand, it's really time for a spring clean to declutter our lives.
我敢肯定，我们很多人都有太多实际上并不使用的东西，当这些东西开始变得失控时，真的是时候进行一些春季大扫除来整理我们的生活了。
However, deciding which items to get rid of can be tricky especially if you are materialistic, believing that physical possessions are the most important thing in life.
然而，决定该扔掉哪些东西可能会很棘手，尤其如果你是个物质主义者，认为物质财富是生活中最重要的东西。
Also, some people are sentimental about letting go of their personal property.
而且，有些人对丢弃自己的个人财产很多愁善感。
But if you haven't got room in your house to move, it's time to evaluate what is really important to you and decide what are your prized possessions and what is just junk.
但是如果你家里连走动的空间都没有了，那就该评估一下什么对你来说才是真正重要的，并且确定哪些是你珍贵的财产，哪些只是垃圾。
Instead of just chucking it away and filling up landfill sites, items could be recycled or given to a charity to re-sell.
与其只是把东西扔掉，填满垃圾填埋场，不如把这些物品回收利用，或者捐给慈善机构再出售。
You could also make some money by using websites where people are willing to pay for second-hand goods.
你也可以通过一些网站赚钱，在这些网站上，人们愿意购买二手物品。
Some people have taken a minimalist approach, deliberately trying to keep life simple.
有些人采取了极简主义的方式，刻意让生活保持简单。
Bea Johnson, author of Zero Waste Home, has done this.
《零浪费家庭》一书的作者比阿·约翰逊就是这样做的。
She says "we've asked really true questions, and evaluated every single thing that we have.
她说：“我们问了非常真实的问题，并评估我们所拥有的每一件东西。
There is nothing that we overlooked.
我们没有忽略任何东西。
I even came to look at my vegetable peeler for example and asked myself, 'do I really need that vegetable peeler?'"
比如，我甚至会看着我的削皮器，问自己，‘我真的需要那个削皮器吗？’”
Of course, if you're a shopaholic or a fashion-victim it's hard to stop buying and shopping online makes purchasing stuff very easy.
当然，如果你是个购物狂或者时尚受害者，就很难停止购物，而且网上购物让购买东西变得非常容易。
James Wallman is a writer and journalist - he questions what we actually need.
詹姆斯·沃尔曼是一位作家兼记者，他质疑我们真正需要的东西是什么。
He says "I'm not anti-stuff - stuff is good.
他说：“我并不反对物质——物质是好的。
I'm anti too much stuff and I'm anti the wrong stuff.
我反对的是太多的物质，以及错误的物质。
Don't go out and buy that labelled good that you think is going to make people think something more of you.
不要出去买那些你认为会让别人对你另眼相看的名牌商品。
That's not going to make you happy."
那不会让你快乐。”
This sounds like good advice.
这听起来是很好的建议。
It's good to take stock of what we have and what we really need.
评估一下我们所拥有的和我们真正需要的东西是有好处的。
But there are still some things I just can't face parting company with; my CD collection, even though I now download my music, and my childhood teddy bear.
但是仍然有一些东西我实在无法割舍，比如我的CD收藏，尽管我现在都是下载音乐，还有我童年时的泰迪熊。
What about you - have you got something that you just can't throw away?
你呢，你有没有什么东西是你就是舍不得扔掉的？